ALLISON P. THOMAS

1023 Longview Drive West Chester, PA 19380 Athomasartistics@gmail.com :: [484] 354.2839

Qualification Summary: Goal-oriented with comprehensive customer service, human relations, and childhood development experience. Dedicated to art education and thrives to inspire children through relevant units. Works well alone but excels within a team setting. Demonstrates responsibility, flexibility, dependability, and is competent in completing tasks.

Work Experience:

2015-Present Porsche of The Main Line, Newtown Square, PA

Service Coordinator/Writer

- Great customers and direct them in the correct direction.
- Answer phones and coordinate service appointments
- Write up repair orders and prepare estimates.
- Maintain and coordinate loaner fleet
- Push shop productivity and drive business
- Manage people and execute leadership roles

2010-2015 Otto's Imported Cars, Exton, PA

Service Writer (PT/FT)

- Greet customers in a friendly productive manner
- Communicates with customer, document concerns, and relay information to technicians.
- Guide clients and answer questions regarding service, and parts
- Build estimates and guide shop productivity

2013-2014 Bethel Springs Elementary School, Garnet Valley, PA

P/T Elementary Art Teacher

- Create, Modify, execute lesson plans
- Manage classroom duties and expectations
- Assess student growth, implement PA standards
- Nurture creative growth
- Provide a safe environment for students
- Maintain open relationships with students and their mentors

2007-2010 Mercedes Benz of Devon, Devon, PA

Customer Service Representative

- Welcomed customers while tending to each clients comfort and needs
- Responsible for gathering the necessary paperwork on a day to day basis for each appointment
- Ability to understand the product and its information in order to translate and assist clientele
- Handling all forms of payment while insuring accurate billing and client specific information

Education:

2010-2011 Maryland Institute College of Art (MICA) Baltimore, MD

Master of Arts in Teaching program (MAT)

Maryland Certification K-12 Pennsylvania Certification K-12

2006-2010 Maryland Institute College of Art (MICA) Baltimore, MD

Bachelors of Fine Art (BFA)

2002-2006 B. Reed Henderson High School, West Chester, PA,

Diploma

References:

Anna Cunningham Founder of Hop Toad Studio Chester Springs 971.678.5970

Tara Allen Assistant Principal Bethel Springs Elementary School Garnet Valley School District 610.579.3000

Steve Piasecki Principal Bethel Springs Elementary School Garnet Valley School District 610.579.3000

April Simpson Mentor Teacher/friend Middle School Art, Howard County Baltimore 410.382.7564